Are you tired of using the eyelash curler everyday, and wondering if you can permanently curl your eyelashes?
I'm C.G, with Lips and More.
Can you permanently curl your eyelashes?
That's the question.
Well, actually no.
It's like perming your hair.
A perm does not last in your hair indefinitely.
Hair grows out, your perm grows out.
Also, if you don't take care of your hair, and the perm, it's not going to last as long, either.
Same way with your eyelashes.
The procedure for eyelash perming, is finding a professional, talking with that person, making sure they know what they're going to do.
Have them explain the procedure to you, which is when they're going to perm your eyelashes, they're going to clean the eye area, protect the eye area, and have you keep your eyes closed, for the full process, and procedure.
They're going to use little tiny rollers there, and then they're going to apply the chemical.
Now, your eyelashes are going to only stay permed four to eight weeks, because eyelashes regrow.
They come out, and they'll regrow, but that growth does finally end, and the perm will end.
You'll have to have it redone again, so this is C.G, with Lips and More, and the greatest gift, is the gift of beauty.